Guide to the Records of the Communications Workers of America, Local 1150 WAG.059
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Minutes, 1940-1984
  - Transit Strike Meetings, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 6b)
  - Membership Committee, 1952, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Overtime Equalization Committee, Plant Section (with correspondence to 1963), 1952, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Seniority of Hours Committee, Traffic Section, 1940-1956 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Social Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Strike Committee, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vacation Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 11a)
  - Welfare Committee, [1951-1953] (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - NYC Area Council and Downstate, 1955-1965 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Essex-West Hudson Labor Council AFL-CIO (NJ), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Series III: Correspondence, 1939-1986
  - FLLTW National Office, NYC, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - FLLTW and NFTW National Office, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - FLLTW National Office, NYC with local officers (Branches 101 & 127), Dec 1942-May 1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - FLLTW: Office management corresp., 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - FLLTW Branch 127 with other Branches, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - FLLTW Branch 127 with Branch representatives, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - FLLTW Branch 127 with members, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - FLLTW Branch 127 re: "Maternity Temporary" employees, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - FLLTW Branch 127, general, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - FLLTW Traffic Branch 101, general, 1943-1946 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - FLLTW Branch 7001 & AUTW Local 1: Chairman's corresp., 1942-1946 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - ATTIS, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 25a)
  - AUTW National Office, NYC (incl. reports), 1946, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - AUTW Local 1, 1946-1950 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, Jun 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1952-Mar-55 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, Jul 1955-Apr 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1956-1958 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1966-Jul 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, Aug 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1974-Jul 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, Aug 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC, 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CWA (International), Washington, DC (Legislative/PAC material), 1950-1975, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CWA, Secretary-Treasurer, 1952-1956, 1959-1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - CWA, Secretary-Treasurer, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - CWA, Secretary-Treasurer, 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - CWA, Secretary-Treasurer, 1970-1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, Jun 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: Bargaining Unit, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: Bargaining Unit, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: Bargaining Unit, 1968-1975, 1978, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: Bargaining Unit, 1971-1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: National Director, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - CWA, Long Lines National Office: National Director, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CWA District 1, May 1951-1955 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - CWA District 1, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - CWA District 1, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - CWA District 1, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - CWA District 1, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - CWA District 1, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - CWA District 1, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - CWA District 1, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - CWA District 1, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CWA District 1, 1973-1974, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1946-1953 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1954-1959 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1960-1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Local Officers: President/Vice-President, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1956-1961 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1962-1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1968-1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Local Officers with Management, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Local Secretary-Treasurer, 1953-1966 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Local Secretary-Treasurer, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Local Secretary-Treasurer, 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board, 1979-1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Insurance Committee, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Local Committee Members, 1946-1959 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Committee, [1946-1972] (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Organizing & Education Committees, 1946-1959 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Organizing & Education Committees, 1961-1967, 1971-1975, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1962-1963, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Social Committee, 1946-1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Committee, 1953, 1957-1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Section Chair, 1955, 1960-1970, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Plant Section Chair, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Plant Section Chair, 1952-1953, 1960-1975, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Traffic Section Chair, 1950, [1953-1974], 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Stewards, 1945-1949 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Stewards, 1950-1953 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Stewards, 1955-1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Stewards, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Stewards, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Stewards, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Stewards, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Stewards, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Stewards, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Members, 1951-1956 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Members, 1957-1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Members, 1960-1966 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Members, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Members, 1970-1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Members, 1978-1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Members' resignations, 1948-1956 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Members' resignations, 1957-1974, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Life Membership File, 1959, 1961-1965 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Life Membership File, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Life Membership File, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - AUTW & CWA locals, 1946-1950 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - CWA locals, 1951-1962 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - CWA locals, 1965-1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Office Employees International Union (Locals 344 & 153), 1959-1965 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Other unions, 1946- 1951 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Other unions, 1955-1959, 1961-1965, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - NYC Central Labor Council, 1960-1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NYC Central Labor Council, 1970-1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - NY State CIO Council, 1955, 1957, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - NJ State CIO Council, 1957-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - NY State Dept. of Labor, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - US Dept. of Labor, 1958, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Attorneys, 1955-1984 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - General correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - General correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - General correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - General correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Series IV: Election and Referendum Records, 1946-1990
  - Elections Committee, Manual (notes & drafts), undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Balloting Committee: reports, etc., 1946-1955 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Balloting Summaries, local and national, 1946-1953 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - AUTW Local 1 & CWA Local 1150: election results, 1946-1954 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Elections Committee: correspondence, 1946-1952 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Elections Committee: correspondence: ballots, resolutions, and membership lists, 1946-1951 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - AUTW Local 1, Elections, 1947-1949 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Balloting Committee: corresp. and report, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - AUTW Local 1, Letters of notification, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Elections Committee: corresp., reports, ballots, 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Elections Committee: corresp., reports, ballots, 1954-1955, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Elections, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - General Election: notices, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - General Election: notices and Convention: notices, reports, and corresp., 1956 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Elections Committee, 1956-1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - General Election: corresp., report, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Convention delegates, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - General Elections: results, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Referendum, strike vote, contract ratification, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - General Elections: corresp., 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Referenda, Special Election, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Referenda, elections, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Elections, contract ratification, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Elections, contract ratification, 1962-1963, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Elections, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Special Election, 1963, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Elections, Contract Ratification, 1964, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Dues Increase Referendum, 1960, 1965-1966, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Elections, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Elections, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Elections, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Special Election, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Elections Committee, 1962-1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - General Election, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Elections, referenda, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Special Election, 1975, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Elections, referenda, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Elections, 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Elections (challenged), 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Elections, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Stewards: reports on additions and changes, 1967-1976, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Campaign materials, 1957-1979 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Campaign materials, 1980, 1984, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Series V: Financial Records [See also Local and International Secretary-Treasurers' Correspondence in Series III], 1939-1988
  - Notes on dues rates, 1939-1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - FLLTW and AUTW, Treasurer's Reports, 1940-1958 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - AUTW Local 1: reports, etc., 1946-1950 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - AUTW Local 1: receipts for expenses, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - AUTW Local 1: dues in arrears, Jan 1949-Apr 1949 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - AUTW Local 1: dues in arrears, May 1949-Apr 1950 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - AUTW Local 1: dues in arrears: dues payments, Jan 1951-Mar 1951 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: dues payments, Apr 1951-Jun 1951 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: committee reports & proposals, 1951-1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: reports of annual audit, 1952-1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: monthly reports, 1949-1955 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: defense fund, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: monthly reports, 1960-1964, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: monthly reports, 1979, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: recruiting incentives, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - CWA Local 1150: chart of accounts: report forms and regulations, 1961-1965 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - CWA (International): auditor's annual reports, 1952-1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - CWA (International): Finance Committee documents & Ways and Means Committee report, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Series VI: Bargaining and Arbitration Records, 1944-1986
  - Agreement: AT&T, Long Lines Dept. and FLLTW, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Articles of Agreement: General Routine and Plant Routines; Contract Provisions, 1944-1947 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Contracts; Agreements, 1944-1946, 1957, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Contracts; Agreements, 1948-1953 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Contracts; Agreements, 1948-1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Contracts; Agreements, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Memos of Agreement, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Memos of Agreement, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Bargaining demands, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining demands, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining reports, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining demands, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining reports, 1956-1958 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining demands, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - International Bargaining for 1957 Contract, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining demands and reports, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining demands and reports, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining reports, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining demands and proposed contract, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Bargaining and contract ratification, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - American Arbitration Assn. referendum on contract ratification, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining Report, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining Reports, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - CWA correspondence with Local 1150; management bargaining reports, 1967-1968, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining reports and correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining demands, reports, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining demands and correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Bargaining reports and correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Bargaining demands, reports, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Bargaining Demands, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Bargaining Demands, 1980, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Bargaining, 1980, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Bargaining, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Bargaining I, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining II, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Contracts and Agreements: Union Proposal and Correspondence, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Contracts, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Memo of Agreement and correspondence, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Memo of Agreement, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Wage Schedules, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Wage Reopener, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Wage Reopener, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Wage Reopener, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1967-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration Awards: Local 1101, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration Awards: Locals 1102, 1103, 1104, 1972-1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration Awards: Local 1106, 1972-1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Awards: Locals 1107, 1108, 1109, 1120, 1122, 1126, 2205, 1969-1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration Awards: Local 1150, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 5a)
  - Arbitration Awards: Locals 1170, 1180, 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Misc. agreements with AT&T, 1952-1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Company policies and agreements: Division Level (Traffic Chairman's File), 1952-1961 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration cases, 1966-1968, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration case (re: drug use) pp. 1-187, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Arbitration case (re: drug use) pp. 188-349, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration case (re: drug use) pp. 350-end, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Cases, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration case (re: human rights law) I, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 13a)
  - Arbitration case (re: human rights law) II, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 13b)
  - Arbitration Cases, 1978-1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Award Summaries, 1979-1984 (Box 16, Folder 14a)
- Series VII: Strikes and Work Stoppages, 1944-1983
  - Ohio Federation, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Illinois Telephone Traffic Union Strike; ACEW Strike; Kearney Case, 1945-1947 (Box 17, Folder 1a)
  - New York City Strike Report, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Work Assignments, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Strike Welfare Fund, 1952-1954 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - General Telephone of CA Strike; White Plains Traffic Section Strike, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - New York Telephone Company Lockout, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - New York Plant Strike Settlement, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - White Plains Traffic Section Strike, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bell System Strike, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - New York Telephone Company Lockout, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Western Electric Strike, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - New York Plant Strike, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - O'Neil-Campbell affair, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Strike Vote, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - District 1 Strike Bulletins, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Easter Traffic problem, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - AT&T Long Lines Work Stoppage, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Legal/Liability, 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Strike Benefits, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Strike Bulletins, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Strike Preparation, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Series VIII: Convention and Conference Records, 1944-1988
  - NFTW, 10th National Convention, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - FLLTW, 1st Annual Convention, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - AUTW-CIO Convention: report by VP C. Allen, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - AUTW, TWOC-CIO, Presidents' Conference: report, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - CWA, Founding Convention, proceedings, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1950, 1952-1954 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1952-1955 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1961-1963 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1970, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1973-1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - CWA National Conventions, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - CWA National Community Services Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - CWA National Conference on Minority Concerns, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - CWA National C.S.I. Conference, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - CWA Special Convention on the Future, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - CWA Local Presidents' Conference on Collective Bargaining, Oct 8, 1988-Oct 9, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - CWA Legislative-Political Conferences, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - CWA Legislative-Political Conferences, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - CWA Legislative-Political Conferences, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - CWA New Jersey State Conference, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - CWA Organizing-Training Conferences, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Long Island Federation of Labor Convention, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Long Lines: ATTCOM Leadership Conference, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Long Lines: Northeast Caucus, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Long Lines: Operators Services Conference, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Long Lines Presidents' Conferences: Minutes, 1952, 1955-1956, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1964-1965, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1972, 1974-1977 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1978-1980 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Long Lines: President's Conference, 1981-1984, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Long Lines: Administrative Conference, 1979, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Long Lines: Traffic Conferences, 1977, 1979-1983 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - District One: Leadership Conferences, 1976-1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - District One: Leadership Conferences, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - District One: Women's Activity Conference, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, 1976, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Legislative Conference, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - I.U.D. Regional Safety Conference, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - National Women's Conference, 1977, 1979, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Conference on Technology, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Series IX: Subject Files, 1941-1989
  - Absence Control Program, 1967, 1977, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Absenteeism, report by J. Guinan, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Activity Log (Anna R. Szabo), 1949-1951 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Activity Report, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Allied & Technical Workers, Distr. 50, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - American Bell Co., 1982 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - American Red Cross, 1958-1969 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Anticipated Disability Program (ADP), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Apparatus Cleaners and Mechanics, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Rights, 1977, 1979, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Assignment of Tours, 1943-1946 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Assignment of Tours, 1947-1951 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Assignment of Tours, 1952-1954 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Assignment of Tours, 1956-1965, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - ATTCOM, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 21)